And we also can add our images as elements.
So that's also doable.
For example, you have a badge or you have a logo or whatever,
which is transparent as well.
And you wanna add it on top of these layers.
All you need to do is say you need to come to here,
come to elements and click on add your images.
And then you'll be able to upload it
from your device, wherever that it is, right?
So I close this one.
What else do we have?
You have uploads, so in this part,
we can upload images as well.
In this part, actually, we can upload images as well
by clicking on this image.
But when we were in elements, that's a little bit different.
Because here we're adding images, but in that term,
in that section, and in that part, we're adding elements.
These are known as two different things
when it comes to this photo editor tool.